Hi guys, finally we're live. It took a little longer. We had a few technical difficulties.
the soundboard suddenly disappeared. We're sorry. We're sorry. We're doing this for the first time with
a little better technology and more technology and another program, so we hope
that everything is working out now. And we hope that you understand us. So if not,
please write it in the comments, let us know. But we hope it works
all. You can hear and see us. Okay, so in English, hey guys, sorry for the delay. We had some technical issues here
because the sound was gone suddenly and we had no idea why and we're testing new
equipment and new software so I hope everything works and I hope you can hear
us and see us you can leave a comment saying hi and yeah we're going to speak
in German today mainly because we're both from Germany and I'll try to
translate in between a bit but yeah stay tuned we're going to show you some
pictures from the last day so you don't have to understand everything.
Yeah, yeah. I don't know, should we start? Who am I? Who are you? Let's start with that.
Yeah, let's do that right away. I'm Fuxi, hi! Maybe you've seen me on one or the other
seen another picture of Celine or in a video or something like that. Yes, and I'm
just here to visit and we have been working hard for you the last few days
collected content, created and yes, we have, among other things, made pictures with it.
with both... oh god, these are already spots for makeup!
Mmm, yummy!
Or with this...
and of course...
with this.
That's why we put together some pictures for you.
Take a quick look at them, quickly in English.
fun and you can see a slideshow of the pictures now.
Thanks for watching!
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to the finished pictures.
Yes, we are also very, very excited.
Yes, I'm just seeing one of the comments, of course, again, whether we are siblings.
No, no.
We are not sisters. We are not related at all.
Sisters not twins?
Not cousins, not even cousins.
No, we are not twins.
Sister from another mystery.
So I mean, we both have red hair.
We are both pale.
And we are both about the same size.
But that's it.
She has blue eyes, I have brown eyes.
We have completely different facial shapes.
Red tones, I'm so yellow.
You're not.
I'm a pink swan.
But that's it, to be honest.
We would understand each other great if that was enough to be siblings.
I don't think so.
I also think less.
No.
So, yeah, we're not siblings.
Not at all.
But, uh...
Look at your Paradise pants.
One of the two pants is actually from Paradise.
But your screen is off.
My screen is off.
I can't see.
Ah, it's back.
Yes, that's yours.
Yes.
My pants are from Paradise, actually.
This is the Winter Leggings from Paradise. I can really recommend it. I already have it on today and on the days. Also on the road and outside.
Mine is from Sleekchic. Also very chic. As you can see, not with the seams, but just very thin fabric.
It looks very nice on the skin, on the body. It's wonderful. Wonderful. Wonderful. Wonderful.
Wonderful! I like, I like, I like, I like!
Beautiful!
Oh my god, I can see right now that we have 280 viewers at this time!
What would be interesting would be where you guys come from!
Where are you guys from?
We just talked about our pants because there was a question if one of us is wearing paradise pants.
I am. She's wearing a sleek cheek, leggings and she just asked where you guys from.
from so type it in the comments here and because we're curious it's already 284
people watching this which makes us pretty happy so tell us a bit about
where you're from and I'm going to talk about her now or with her about her
There were always a lot of questions. We actually did a Q&A series on Instagram.
And I think the biggest question is always what Soviet models actually drive.
To take away a little bit, we are not mainly models.
Exactly. We both have a normal full-time job and do the whole thing because we enjoy it,
because we like the materials we wear on our bodies, because we like to model,
like the photos, like the material on the photos, like to be booked for fashion shows.
And that usually also applies to the fetish model jobs that you have there.
You come to festivals or parties for free, if you work there.
You can also take a friend or partner with you.
It's a lot of fun.
You get to know a lot of people in the scene.
I think I know someone in every bigger city in Germany.
And that's how you look around. That's why I'm actually here now.
We also met through modeling.
Through a show actually.
Through a show.
In latex.
On a WGT in latex.
That's how the circle closes and the question is actually answered.
real full-time models but we're doing this as a hobby.
Oh, I have a drink here.
So we're doing this as a hobby,
we're not earning money with our photo shoots,
we're doing this for fun because we like it,
because we like to wear the stuff,
because we like to show the stuff and take pictures
and to go on shows.
Parties.
Parties, meet great people there.
So no, we're both having normal day jobs,
we're actually normal people
who happen to make pictures and happen to like what they do
yeah that's actually quite the most of it
from Poland, Netherlands, Italy oh my gosh
I have to say I'm wearing... USA!
yeah we're 300... 200... USA!
I have to say I'm not wearing my glasses and I couldn't find my lenses so I'm not saying anything
I didn't wear glasses and contact lenses anymore and now I can't read it, only you can.
I'm trying to share it.
I see right now we have an incredible number of viewers from Denmark, Denmark, from the USA, New Jersey, from Canada,
from Germany, from North Germany, nice, hello!
I'm originally from North Germany too.
Nice!
Singapore! Nice! Wow, hi! Thanks a lot for tuning in!
Do you have any more questions for me, since we're already here?
How did you come to become a model or a fetish model?
That's a funny story. I actually started both at the same time.
My first photo shoot was at the same time my first fetish shoot and my first contact was a bondage shoot.
It was a day of open doors and I thought, okay, I'll take the opportunity to observe the different photographers and models and take a look at them.
What can I say? I couldn't look so quickly, I was already hanging from the ceiling.
It sounds worse than it is. I wasn't forced or anything.
It was super cool and since then I've been both
being infected and
photoshotting infected
and I think that took about half a year, three quarters of a year
and then I had my first latex shooting
Okay, so she just told me that she
started doing photoshoots and all the future stuff together
and she quite liked it
and was really into it so she continued doing this
and for how long are you doing this now?
And my first photoshoot was in 2016.
So since 2016 already.
And yeah, I'll put your glass away again.
Thank you.
No problem.
Yes, we actually tried to prepare a little bit for the whole thing here.
Among other things with the technology, which hopefully is now working.
Hopefully still.
Oh, hello, I get a hello back.
Very nice.
We asked Celine and me on our Instagram channel if there are some tasks that we can do for you guys
so that we can tweet you guys a little bit for watching us right now
and we actually got a lot of tasks that we wrote down for the others
from us what we should do and you send a lot of suggestions and we wrote them down and
we're going to draw and pick one yeah we're going to pick one task for each of us. I have the tasks
the Nox tasks, I have the fox tasks. Should I start?
Mine, okay.
You can start with mine.
Come on, I'm the host, start with mine.
Okay.
Fox challenge!
Oh yeah!
Okay, put on ballet heels and stand there for 3 seconds.
So her challenge is to wear some ballet heels and stand up for like 3 seconds.
three seconds and you've never worn ballet heels before?
I've never worn ballet heels before!
She's never worn ballet heels before!
So please don't laugh at me
if I can't do it.
I have my full respect for all the women
who can do this.
Oh god, oh god!
Look! I've already prepared something for you.
Oh no!
I just quite recently
tried it myself in a video on this channel
and it was like, oh, wow!
Ah!
Luckily we have almost the same size of the shoe. Hopefully.
I think it's already overlaid.
So, how does it feel?
Super unusual.
But it's pretty. It's very pretty.
It makes an aesthetic...
Do you have a lot of lactic oil on your feet?
Yes, I also take care of my leather pants.
It makes a very nice foot.
The task was to stand.
Like a penguin.
And I'm getting a cramp.
Okay, so again, my biggest respect to all the women who can do this.
I didn't think you could do this.
You've given me the most difficult task.
I didn't think she could do it. I'm actually super surprised that she could even walk.
Like what?
So, I have fulfilled my task!
What do the people say about it?
The heels look great on you!
Thank you!
They really make a nice leg!
Don't break your feet!
I tried my very best!
Thank you!
She's still alive, the feet are still on!
So they're still healthy!
So, that brings us to your task!
I have fulfilled my task!
Let's see if you can do it too!
but also great suggestions
So, your Nox challenge
is to put on a catsuit in 30 seconds
was like yeah you should wear latex catsuit in 30 seconds I was like that's not possible
impossible yeah the person who sent me the challenge said I should wear latex catsuit
in 30 seconds and it doesn't work so I've worn latex outfits in my life enough
to know 30 seconds for latex catsuit latex maybe but then only a slip
or chlorinated I don't have a chlorinated catsuit for example but we also have one
which looks beautiful. It's also shiny. It's almost latex. Can I take this off before?
No, it's on the sign. The audience should decide that now. But I think it's okay if you take it off.
Do you have a stopwatch? It's about putting it on. I have to take everything off anyway.
I would take my stopwatch off. Because I want to do it.
Oh yeah, this one is quite nice actually.
It's Ketsuit by Elysee.
Well, it's PVC. It's not latex, it's PVC.
You should have had a sip before.
So if you just turned in, now we're doing a little challenge here.
I have to change into Ketsuit in 30 seconds.
And I hope everything works with the tech stuff and so on.
because, yeah, we're just having a bit of fun here.
So for all of you who just came along, we've already talked a little bit about
how we drove for days, because Fuchsie visited me and she had to
put on ballet heels and now I have to... And I did it!
I did it! I think you'll be with me forever. You know each other so well!
Who would have thought, I have to change in 30 seconds. So, my timer is set, I'll just take
the drink just immediately again from a safe look ok i have to save the customers
where it goes but it's getting more and more shabby
what she does there
i was not trained before i was allowed to try out the tasks that are set for us and
thought okay maybe i can do that now what you have already tried out i was not allowed
I wasn't allowed to try it out. Okay, 30 seconds, yes? Yes. And go! The time is running.
Oh god, I'm already hanging on a t-shirt. You should see it. It's just a wild mess of clothes
I see it flies half in my direction
Okay, you still have exactly
Exactly a
Yes, one arm wasn't in there.
Well, but you have to say that it's beautiful to look at.
That was really 30 seconds.
That felt so much shorter.
At this point I would like to note that I have completed my challenge.
Yes, yes.
And you didn't.
I will be a commentator.
Yes, I think so too.
Can you help me? No. No? Okay. So I did not win my challenge.
Shame on me.
I will have so much fun with the next years that I have done it and you haven't.
But I'm shining for that now. So beautiful.
So beautiful shining.
I would say it's a bit sweaty now. But we're dressed beautifully. I can check again if we have any new comments.
Hmm, nice catsuit. The catsuit looks great. There's a sign on top, that's right.
That's right, it's brand new. It's just unpacked.
Yes, and it's actually very comfortable.
And you can also look forward to a jumpsuit with this jumpsuit.
And there is actually a comment that says it was almost impossible to pull it out.
So maybe it was actually about the outfit of the catsuit.
I have to admit that changing clothes was already a mean thing.
Yes.
But yes, you see how I read it several times, it looks great in the catsuit.
Thank you.
It was a bit mean that I had to get rid of all my clothing first and then get into the catsuit
If I would have to just put the catsuit on for 30 seconds that would be doable
But with all the changing and stuff like that and latex, no way
It takes like five minutes to get into like six catsuits
Yeah if you don't want to sweat to death when you hurry
Or to rip it
Yeah
I'm also warm now.
You said it.
Well, then I would say we'll have a cool down.
I hope...
Cheers.
I hope you had fun.
It was my first time with you on YouTube live.
We've tried a video together.
Yes, the latex girlfriend video with you is on my channel.
How to get your girlfriend to wear latex.
There's already a video with her on my channel.
how to get my girlfriend into latex in German because yeah obviously we're from
Germany and if you want to check that one out or the other videos or leave us
a comment under this livestream or check out her social media I think I already
linked it in the description of the video
Yes, and I think we can tell you that much already. There will also be another video.
Whaaat? What?
Yes, we have worked on it the last few days, filmed, produced content for you.
The last few days. Yesterday.
Today too. Minimally.
Today we took beautiful pictures, yesterday we took beautiful pictures and shot a beautiful video.
Completely in selfie style with a lot of latex.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
The squirrel is called Ronaldo.
So, yeah.
Maybe to end the video...
Partner look?
Hmm...
Do I have to do this in 30 seconds too?
No.
But I can also sew it.
That would be great.
So... oh god.
It's all tangled up.
So I just suggested that we're going to do...
Partner looks. Partner looks. But yeah, I'm already stuck in the lacing.
Yeah.
That's not fun. You can actually, you can open it in the front as well.
Yeah. You shouldn't do that, open the corset in the front without lacing it in the back.
Yeah, that's okay. But yeah. See ya!
Okay. Now I have to entertain you by myself.
I hope you follow as well.
In this video I just have to watch her get undressed.
Okay, that was a leggings that flew in.
Yes, there was her leggings.
Now there is a catsuit that you might already know if you were on my channel.
From a John suit.
So she's going to change into a jumpsuit. You already may know, I just have to check the comments without glasses.
The catsuits from shiitake are so beautiful. Yes, that's true.
So yesterday we shot two catsuits and a skirt and another outfit. That was cool.
The sofa party, yes. This is a couch party because we can't go out.
Normally we see each other on various parties throughout the year and now she's visiting me because
sadly we can't go to parties
No parties at the moment, except on the sofa. That's true.
Oh, there you are!
I have to say, this is something that...
What are you doing?
I ran behind the camera. It's a habit of mine. I always run over the camera.
But this is something that wouldn't have been possible in latex so quickly.
This is not latex either.
Yes, but I wouldn't have gotten it in latex so quickly.
Hello?
I have to say, I think it's great!
It's a wet look or something like that.
It's a PVC-like leather.
But I've definitely seen that on you in the videos.
It looks good here too.
It's so good that we have about the same size of clothes.
Otherwise we wouldn't have been able to make this video like this.
No.
But really chic and I think...
...in the twin looks...
Now we're twins again.
No, we're not twins!
We're not even siblings, but she's wearing the same clothing size as I am so she looks great in this one
and you're breathing really heavily with it.
Did you ever have time getting into this one?
It wasn't that hard, it was really relaxing, but I have to say we're really nervous now.
It's really chic, I couldn't decide which one I like better.
Well, which one do you like better?
Which one do you like more? The black and white one or the shiny PVC one?
I think the white stripe alone makes a very nice silhouette.
The zipper in the front always looks good, as you can see.
Now you're going to fight and keep going.
I don't think so. We don't want to disturb YouTube with our look.
There are already opinions about either or.
You're the best! Not yet, but we have minimal delay in the sending and the whole technique.
I'm really glad that it's apparently going well so far.
If I'm reading this correctly, we should definitely repeat the Fox and Nox game.
Nox meets Fox.
You have the same size, you're not different in size.
So we actually differ by 1 cm.
1cm, 1cm, you 172cm and I'm 173cm.
So 173cm, 172cm.
There's no difference.
That doesn't make it any better that we're not twins or siblings.
Also the shoe size is about the same.
The shiny one will obviously...
Oh look, the shiny one and the black-white one both look good.
Both of you are hot.
The shiny cat looks like the one from the Matrix.
Yes, that's true.
But a lot of what glows looks like from Matrix.
I found the suit you styled for Halloween, the coat, the coat.
It looked very Matrix. I thought that was really cool.
I have a similar one from Punk Rave, but made of leather.
But made of leather with shoulder pads.
And it's also very cool. It's already so frack-like with a high cut at the back.
So she just said that she liked my Punk Rave coat I styled for Halloween because it looked like Matrix.
because someone said that my suit here looks like a Matrix outfit
and I was like, yeah most of PVC Chinese top kinda looks like a Matrix outfit
which is by the way a great film
You can't decide
The shiny one could win very close
but the black and white one seems to be exciting too
I think if we leave the game out of the way
we'll go with an undecided one today
Okay, good
We'll wear it together at Harry Potter
We're going to make a mess now.
That's how it looks.
All right.
I hope I didn't hit myself so badly in the video.
No, you didn't.
Wait until we cut the video from yesterday. That will be very funny.
Oh yeah.
You have to say that I do a lot of unfucked shooting.
I do it because I have fun and I really have fun with it.
And I'm a break clown. I was already in school.
having fun I make a lot of fun and that's what we do we have a lot of fun
with what we're doing and so I hope you had a lot of fun with this live stream
as well I hope you had a lot of fun
me too! I definitely could imagine that we would do the game again and maybe go live again
okay so maybe we'll see you guys soon in the meanwhile check out my videos here
the next one is coming on Sunday about this catsuit spoiler alert and the
second catsuit from this brand so yeah stay tuned
also feel like this to shop fashion much good hot lunch in on
Thank you.